A Guide to the Records of Julian A. Burruss, President, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1906-1946
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Series 3: Correspondence
  - Subseries 4: Correspondence, 1922
    - A.B. Thornhill, 1922 (Box-folder 6-360)
    - J.J. Tigert, 1922 (Box-folder 6-361)
    - W.R. Tilson, 1922 (Box-folder 6-362)
    - A.F. Treakle, 1922 (Box-folder 6-363)
    - Governor Trinkle, 1922 (Box-folder 6-364)
      - VPI mine conditions are dangerous
    - E. Lee Trinkle, 1922 (Box-folder 6-365)
    - Clement S. Ucker, 1922 (Box-folder 6-366)
    - Miscellaneous - V, 1922 (Box-folder 6-367)
    - B.H. Van Oot - Railroad strike, 1922 (Box-folder 6-368)
    - Veterans Bureau, 1922 (Box-folder 6-369)
    - Miscellaneous - W, 1922 (Box-folder 6-370)
    - Miss Maggie Wade, 1922 (Box-folder 6-371)
    - War Department, 1922 (Box-folder 6-372)
    - J.W. Watson, 1922 (Box-folder 6-373)
    - Wiley & Wilson, 1922 (Box-folder 6-374)
    - J.E. Williams, 1922 (Box-folder 6-375)
    - F.E. Williford, 1922 (2 folders) (Box-folder 6-376 and 6-376A)
    - R. Holman Willis, 1922 (Box-folder 6-377)
    - S.A. Wingard, 1922 (Box-folder 6-378)
    - T.K. Wolfe, 1922 (Box-folder 6-379)
    - T. Gilbert Wood, 1922 (Box-folder 6-380)
    - A.F. Woods, 1922 (Box-folder 6-381)
    - James P. Woods, 1922 (Box-folder 6-382)
    - Miscellaneous - Y, Z, 1922 (Box-folder 6-383)
  - Subseries 5: Correspondence, 1923
    - Miscellaneous - A, 1923 (Box-folder 6-384)
    - E.A. Alderman, 1923 (Box-folder 6-385)
    - S. Anderson, 1923 (Box-folder 6-386)
    - V.C. Austin, 1923 (Box-folder 6-387)
    - H.C. Barnett, 1923 (Box-folder 6-388)
    - Ethel L. Bedient, 1923 (Box-folder 6-389)
    - R.B.H. Begg, 1923 (Box-folder 6-390)
    - Frances M. Benson, Acting Librarian, 1923 (Box-folder 6-391)
      - Monthly reports for the VPI Library, Agricultural Branch
    - R.E. Blackwell, 1923 (Box-folder 6-392)
    - W.M. Brodie, 1923 (Box-folder 6-393)
    - W.A. Brumfield, 1923 (Box-folder 6-394)
    - O.C. Burkhart, 1923 (Box-folder 6-395)
    - C.G. Burr, 1923 (Box-folder 6-396)
    - Miscellaneous - C, 1923 (Box-folder 6-397)
      - Christo Cola Bottling Co.
    - C&P Telephone Co., 1923 (Box-folder 6-398)
    - W.B. Caggin, 1923 (Box-folder 6-399)
    - Anna Campbell, 1923 (Box-folder 6-4003)
    - Theo. P. Campbell, 1923 (Box-folder 6-401)
    - Chaplains, 1923 (Box-folder 6-402)
    - W.G. Chrisman, 1923 (Box-folder 6-403)
    - L.S. Cottrell, Acting Secretary YMCA, 1923 (Box-folder 6-404)
    - M.M. Davis, 1923 (Box-folder 6-405)
    - Paul N. Derring, 1923 (Box-folder 6-406)
    - A.W. Drinkard, Jr., 1923 (Box-folder 6-407)
    - James Duff, 1923 (Box-folder 6-408)
    - L.P. Edwards, 1923 (Box-folder 6-409)
    - M.H. Eoff, 1923 (Box-folder 6-410)
    - Faculty Blanket Letters, 1923 (Box-folder 6-411)
    - J.G. Ferneyhough, 1923 (Box-folder 6-412)
    - F.D. Fromme, 1923 (Box-folder 6-413)
    - Miscellaneous - G, 1923 (Box-folder 6-414)
      - Personal letter of Gilette re: hazing and blacking (shoe polish) of cadets
    - F.S. Glassett, 1923 (Box-folder 6-415)
    - S. T. Godbey, 1923 (Box-folder 6-416)
    - Rachel E. Gregg, 1923 (Box-folder 6-417)
    - H. Gudheim, 1923 (Box-folder 6-418)
    - Geo. W. Guy, 1923 (Box-folder 6-419)
    - Miscellaneous - H, 1923 (Box-folder 6-420)
    - M.C. Harrison, 1923 (Box-folder 6-421)
    - H.H. Hill, 1923 (Box-folder 6-422)
    - Leroy Hodges, 1923 (Box-folder 6-423)
    - C.W. Holdaway, 1923 (Box-folder 6-424)
    - R. J. Holden, 1923 (Box-folder 6-425)
    - Henry F. Holtz Claw, 1923 (Box-folder 6-426)
    - J.R. Horsely, 1923 (Box-folder 6-427)
    - R. E. Hunt, 1923 (Box-folder 6-428)
    - J.R. Hutcheson, 1923 (Box-folder 6-429)
    - T.B. Hutcheson, 1923 (Box-folder 6-430)
    - Miscellaneous - I, 1923 (Box-folder 6-431)
    - Miscellaneous - J, 1923 (Box-folder 6-432)
    - J.L. Jarman, 1923 (Box-folder 6-433)
    - J.S.A. Johnson, 1923 (Box-folder 6-434)
    - T.C. Johnson, 1923 (Box-folder 6-435)
    - Eleanor I. Jones, 1923 (Box-folder 6-436)
    - T.W. Knote, 1923 (Box-folder 6-437)
    - Geo. W. Koiner, 1923 (Box-folder 6-438)
    - Miscellaneous - L, 1923 (Box-folder 6-439)
    - D.S. Lancaster, 1923 (Box-folder 6-440)
    - W.L. Lancaster, Mayor, 1924 (Box-folder 6-441)
    - Claudius Lee, 1923 (Box-folder 6-442)
    - J. B. McBryde, 1923 (Box-folder 6-443)
    - J.P. McConnell, 1923 (Box-folder 6-444)
    - E.C. Magill, 1923 (Box-folder 6-445)
    - Chas. G. Maphis, 1923 (Box-folder 6-446)
    - C.P. Miles, 1923 (Box-folder 6-447)
    - E.C. Miller, 1923 (Box-folder 7-448)
    - W.P. Moore, 1923 (Box-folder 7-449)
    - Miscellaneous - N, 1923 (Box-folder 7-450)
    - C.M. Newman, 1923 (Box-folder 7-451)
    - W.S. Newman, 1923 (Box-folder 7-452)
    - J.J. Owens, 1923 (Box-folder 7-453)
    - Louis O'Shaughnessy, 1923 (Box-folder 7-454)
    - J.R. Parrott, 1923 (Box-folder 7-455)
    - E.R. Price, 1923 (Box-folder 7-456)
    - H.L. Price, 1923 (Box-folder 7-457)
    - L.T. Price, 1923 (Box-folder 7-458)
    - S.R. Pritchard, 1923 (Box-folder 7-459)
    - Lawrence T. Priddy, 1923 (Box-folder 7-460)
    - W.H. Rasche, 1923 (Box-folder 7-461)
    - C.B. Ross, 1923 (Box-folder 7-462)
    - Miscellaneous - S, 1923 (Box-folder 7-463)
      - Letter of 3/27/23 re: fire in Blacksburg which 'endangered' a large part of town.
      - Cadets & VPI fire-fighting equipment saved the town. No fire company or equipment in town.
    - Oliver J. Sands, 1923 (Box-folder 7-464)
    - W.T. Sanger, 1923 (Box-folder 7-465)
    - W.C. Saunders, 1923 (Box-folder 7-466)
    - W.D. Saunders, 1923 (Box-folder 7-467)
    - W.J. Schoene, 1923 (Box-folder 7-468)
    - C.E. Seitz, 1923 (Box-folder 7-469)
    - T. McN. Simpson, 1923 (Box-folder 7-470)
    - W.L. Skaggs, 1923 (Box-folder 7-471)
    - J.C. Skuse, 1923 (Box-folder 7-472)
    - E.A. Smyth, 1923 (Box-folder 7-473)
    - J. Hop Taft, 1923 (Box-folder 7-474)
    - W.P. Tams, 1923 (Box-folder 7-475)
    - A. F. Treakle, 1923 (Box-folder 7-476)
    - Governor Trinkle, 1923 (Box-folder 7-477)
      - College gymnasium destroyed in fire b/c almost no water available to fight the fire.
      - Includes Trinkle ltr. Concerning fire equipment at VPI and letter to Gov. Trinkle discussing water problems at VPI and detailed proposal for improvements also includes proposal for improvements of fire fighting equipment.
    - A.C. True, 1923 (Box-folder 7-478)
    - B.H. Van Oot, 1923 (Box-folder 7-479)
    - Miscellaneous - W, 1923 (Box-folder 7-480)
    - Maggie Wade, 1923 (Box-folder 7-481)
    - War Department, 1923 (Box-folder 7-482)
    - J.W. Watson, 1923 (Box-folder 7/483)
    - Wiley & Wilson, 1923 (Box-folder 7-484)
    - J.E. Williams, 1923 (Box-folder 7-485)
    - Lulu V. Walker, 1923 (Box-folder 7-486)
    - I.D. Wilson, 1923 (Box-folder 7-487)
    - F.E. Williford, 1923 (Box-folder 7-488)
    - W.G. Wysor, 1923 (Box-folder 7-489)
    - Miscellaneous - Y, 1923 (Box-folder 7-490)
  - Subseries 6: Faculty Correspondence, 1924
    - W.T. Ackerman, 1924 (Box-folder 7-491)
    - W.E. Barlow, 1924 (Box-folder 7-492)
    - R.B.H. Begg, 1924 (Box-folder 7-493)
    - W.A. Brumfield, 1924 (Box-folder 7-494)
    - O.C. Burkhart, 1924 (Box-folder 7-495)
    - J. A Burruss/Dr. J. G. Ferneyhough Controversy, 1924 (Box-folder 7-496)
    - Theo P. Campbell - Dean of College, 1924 (Box-folder 7-497)
    - John R. Castleman, 1924 (Box-folder 7-498)
    - Chaplains, 1924 (Box-folder 7-499)
    - W.B. Coggin, 1924 (Box-folder 7-500)
    - B.C. Cubbage, 1924 (Box-folder 7-501)
    - Milton Cutherell, 1924 (Box-folder 7-502)
    - Deans, 1924 (Box-folder 7-503)
    - A.W. Drinkard, 1924-1926 (Box-folder 7-504)
    - M.H. Eoff, 1924 (Box-folder 7-505)
    - W.T. Ellis, 1924 (Box-folder 7-506)
    - Faculty Blanket Letters, 1924 (Box-folder 7-507)
    - F.D. Fromme, 1924 (Box-folder 7-508)
    - Mrs. J.C. Glassett, 1924 (Box-folder 7-509)
    - H.H. Hill, 1924 (Box-folder 7-510)
    - Mary Hiss, 1924 (Box-folder 7-511)
    - C.W. Holdaway, 1924 (Box-folder 7-512)
    - R.J. Holden, 1924 (Box-folder 7-513)
    - Hallie L. Hughes, 1924 (Box-folder 7-514)
    - R.E. Hunt, 1924 (Box-folder 7-515)
    - John R. Hutcheson, 1924 (Box-folder 7-516)
    - T.B. Hutcheson, 1924 (Box-folder 7-517)
    - Eleanor I. Jones, 1924 (Box-folder 7-518)
    - Geo. A. Jackson, 1924 (Box-folder 7-519)
    - J.S.A. Johnson, 1924 (Box-folder 7-520)
    - H.L. Klug, 1924 (Box-folder 7-521)
    - T.W. Knote, 1924 (Box-folder 7-522)
    - D.S. Lancaster, 1924 (Box-folder 7-523)
    - Claudius Lee, 1924 (Box-folder 7-524)
    - J.B. McBryde, 1924 (Box-folder 7-525)
    - C.R. Mackan, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 7-526)
    - E.C. Magill, 1924 (Box-folder 7-527)
    - W.C. Mallalieu, 1924 (Box-folder 7-528)
    - A.B. Massey, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 7-529)
    - Wm C. Michael, 1924 (Box-folder 7-530)
    - C.P. Miles, 1924 (Box-folder 7-531)
    - E.C. Miller, 1924 (Box-folder 7-532)
    - S.R. Minter, 1924 (Box-folder 7-533)
    - C.A. Montgomery, 1924 (Box-folder 7-534)
    - C.M. Newman, 1924 (Box-folder 7-535)
    - W.S. Newman, 1924 (Box-folder 7-536)
    - Wm R. Nichols, 1924 (Box-folder 7-537)
    - Louis O'Shaughnessy, 1924 (Box-folder 7-538)
    - J.J. Owens, 1924 (Box-folder 7-539)
    - J. R. Parrott, 1924 (Box-folder 7-540)
    - S.R. Pritchard, 1924 (Box-folder 7-541)
    - E.R. Price, 1924 (Box-folder 7-542)
    - H.L. Price, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 7-543)
    - W.H. Rasche, 1924 (Box-folder 7-544)
    - Chas. E. Seitz, 1924 (Box-folder 7-545)
    - W.J. Schoene, 1924 (Box-folder 7-546)
    - E.A. Smyth, 1924 (Box-folder 7-547)
    - H.S. Stahl, 1924 (Box-folder 7-548)
    - Arthur F. Treakle, 1924 (Box-folder 7-549)
    - B.H. Van Oot, 1924 (Box-folder 7-550)
    - Maggie Wade - Registrar's Office, 1924 (Box-folder 7-551)
    - J.E. Williams, 1924 (Box-folder 7-552)
    - F.E. Williford, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 8-553)
    - I.D. Wilson, 1924 (Box-folder 8-554)
    - T.K. Wolfe, 1924 (Box-folder 8-555)
  - Subseries 7: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1924
    - Miscellaneous - A, 1924 (Box-folder 8-556)
      - American Country Life Assn., 1924
    - E.A. Alderman, Pres. of UVA, 1924 (Box-folder 8-557)
    - Miscellaneous - B, 1924 (Box-folder 8-558)
    - J.W. Beatson, National Economic League, 1924 (Box-folder 8-559)
    - Bettye Bell, 1924 (Box-folder 8-560)
    - R.E. Blackwell, 1924 (Box-folder 8-561)
    - F.W. Boatwright, 1924 (Box-folder 8-562)
    - J.H. Bradford, 1924 (Box-folder 8-563)
    - Miscellaneous - C, 1924 (Box-folder 8-564)
    - Anna Campbell, 1924 (Box-folder 8-565)
    - Adele Clark, 1924 (Box-folder 8-566)
    - W.G. Chrisman, Mayor, 1924 (Box-folder 8-567)
    - Miscellaneous - D, 1924 (Box-folder 8-568)
      - Original ltr. From R. W. Southat, a veteran of Gettysburg in Pickett's Division. He was the last unwounded man to leave the battle alive.
    - Paul N. Derring, 1924 (Box-folder 8-569)
    - Miscellaneous - E, 1924 (Box-folder 8-570)
    - Miscellaneous - F, 1924 (Box-folder 8-571)
      - Acquisition of property (Smithfield)
      - World Peace Mission, 1924
    - J.G. Ferneyhough, 1924 (Box-folder 8-572)
    - Miscellaneous - G, 1924 (Box-folder 8-573)
    - Geological Commission, 1924 (Box-folder 8-574)
    - Miscellaneous - H, 1924 (Box-folder 8-575)
      - Anti-Saloon League of Virginia
      - Fire in Blacksburg at "The Hillside" - Cadets helped
    - C.J. Heatwole, 1924 (Box-folder 8-576)
    - Leroy Hodges, 1924 (Box-folder 8-577)
    - J.R. Horseley, 1924 (Box-folder 8-578)
    - W. C. John, 1924 (Box-folder 8-579)
      - Letters re: the education of 'Negroes' in the South
    - T.C. Johnson, 1924 (Box-folder 8-580)
    - Chapin Jones, 1924 (Box-folder 8-581)
    - Miscellaneous - K, 1924 (Box-folder 8-582)
    - G.W. Koiner, 1924 (Box-folder 8-583)
    - Miscellaneous - L, 1924 (Box-folder 8-584)
      - Barracks Fire
    - Miscellaneous - M, 1924 (Box-folder 8-585)
    - Chas. G. Maphis, 1924 (Box-folder 8-586)
    - J.P. McConnell, 1924 (Box-folder 8-587)
    - J.H. Meek, 1924 (Box-folder 8-588)
    - J.H. Montgomery, 192 (Box-folder 8-589)
    - Miscellaneous - N, 1924 (Box-folder 8-590)
    - J.L. Newcomb, 1924 (Box-folder 8-591)
    - E.W. Nichols, 1924 (Box-folder 8-592)
    - C.A. Osborne, Extension Work, 1924 (Box-folder 8-593)
    - Miscellaneous - P, 1924 (Box-folder 8-594)
    - L.T. Price, 1924 (Box-folder 8-595)
    - Walter M. Priddy, 1924 (Box-folder 8-596)
    - Miscellaneous - R, 1924 (Box-folder 8-597)
    - R.I. Roop, 1924 (Box-folder 8-598)
    - L.S Rowe, 1924 (Box-folder 8-599)
    - Miscellaneous - S, 1924 (Box-folder 8-600)
      - Biography of David Franklin Houston by Harvard classmate submitted by Lewis G. Stevenson. Woodrow Wilson felt Mr. Houston is the best qualified man in the United States to be President.
    - Oliver J. Sands, 1924 (Box-folder 8-601)
    - W.T. Sanger, 1924 (Box-folder 8-602)
    - W.C. Saunders, 1924 (Box-folder 8-603)
    - Claude A. Swanson, 1924 (Box-folder 8-604)
    - W.P. Tams, 1924 (Box-folder 8-605)
    - J.J. Tigert, 1924 (Box-folder 8-606)
    - R.H. Tucker, 1924 (Box-folder 8-607)
    - Miscellaneous - W, 1924 (Box-folder 8-608)
    - War Department, 1924 (Box-folder 8-609)
    - Miscellaneous - Y, Z, 1924 (Box-folder 8-610)
  - Subseries 8: Correspondence, 1925
    - H.C. Ahalt, 1925 (Box-folder 8-611)
    - W.E. Barlow, 1925 (Box-folder 8-612)
    - J.A. Brame, 1925 (Box-folder 8-613)
    - R.B.H. Begg, 1925 (Box-folder 8-614)
    - W.A. Brumfield, 1925 (Box-folder 8-615)
    - W.M. Brodie, 1925 (Box-folder 8-616)
    - Ralph M. Brown, Librarian, 1925 (Box-folder 8-617)
    - F.A. Buchanan, 1925 (Box-folder 8-618)
    - O.C. Burkhart, 1925 (Box-folder 8-619)
    - Theo. P. Campbell, 1925 (Box-folder 8-620)
    - J.R. Castleman, 1925 (Box-folder 8-621)
    - L.I. Case, 1925 (Box-folder 8-622)
    - Chaplains, 1925 (Box-folder 8-623)
    - W.B. Coggin, 1925 (Box-folder 8-624)
    - W.G. Comer, 1925 (Box-folder 8-625)
    - B.C. Cubbage, 1925 (Box-folder 8-626)
    - H.G. Cutright, 1925 (Box-folder 8-627)
    - M.M. Davis, 1925 (Box-folder 8-628)
    - Deans, 1925 (Box-folder 8-629)
    - A.L. Dean, 1925 (Box-folder 8-630)
    - Martha Dinwiddie, 1925 (Box-folder 8-631)
      - Women students
      - Women scholarships
    - A.W. Drinkard, 1925 (Box-folder 8-632)
    - Ester Derring, 1925 (Box-folder 8-633)
    - L.P. Edwards, 1925 (Box-folder 8-634)
    - W.B. Ellett, 1925 (Box-folder 8-635)
    - W.T. Ellis, 1925 (Box-folder 8-636)
    - M.H. Eoff, 1925 (Box-folder 8-637)
    - Faculty Blanket Letters, 1925 (Box-folder 8-638)
    - F.D. Fromme, 1925 (Box-folder 8-639)
    - W.E. Garnett, 1925 (Box-folder 8-640)
    - Harry Gudheim, 1925 (Box-folder 8-641)
    - W.C. Hallalieu, 1925 (Box-folder 8-642)
    - Anna G. Hannas, 1925 (Box-folder 8-643)
    - M.C. Harrison, 1925 (Box-folder 8-644)
    - T.W. Hatcher, 1925 (Box-folder 8-645)
    - F.B. Haynes, 1925 (Box-folder 8-646)
    - Marshall Hendrick, 1925 (Box-folder 8-647)
    - D.C. Heitshu, 1925 (Box-folder 8-648)
    - Mary Hiss, 1925 (Box-folder 8-649)
    - H.H. Hill, 1925 (Box-folder 8-650)
    - C.W. Holdaway - dairy, 1925 (Box-folder 8-651)
    - C.W. Hoilman, 1925 (Box-folder 8-652)
    - R.J. Holden, 1925 (Box-folder 8-653)
    - Hallie L. Hughes, 1925 (Box-folder 8-654)
    - R.E. Hunt, 1925 (Box-folder 8-655)
    - J.R. Hutcheson, 1925 (Box-folder 8-656)
    - Cooperative Ext. in Agric. & Home Economics (Box-folder 8-656A)
    - T.B. Hutcheson, 1925 (Box-folder 8-657)
    - Calvert H. Jenkins, 1925 (Box-folder 8-658)
    - J.B. Jones, 192 (Box-folder 8-659)
    - J.S.A. Johnson, 1925 (Box-folder 8-660)
    - H.L. Klug, 1925 (Box-folder 8-661)
    - Theo W. Knote, 1925 (Box-folder 8-662)
    - D.S. Lancaster, 1925 (Box-folder 8-663)
    - Claudius Lee, 1925 (Box-folder 8-664)
    - J.B. Lucas, 1925 (Box-folder 8-665)
    - Mary B. McGowan, 1925 (Box-folder 8-666)
    - M.J. Markuson, 1925 (Box-folder 8-667)
    - E.C. Magill, 1925 (Box-folder 8-668)
    - C.P. Miles, 1925 (Box-folder 8-669)
    - E.C. Miller, 1925 (Box-folder 9-670)
    - S.R. Minter, 1925 (Box-folder 9-671)
    - A.V. Morris, 1925 (Box-folder 9-672)
    - F.A. Motz, 1925 (Box-folder 9-673)
    - C.M. Newman, 1925 (Box-folder 9-674)
      - Chairman Committee on Social Activities
    - W.S. Newman, 1925 (Box-folder 9-675)
    - W.R. Nichols, 1925 (Box-folder 9-676)
    - Eldona Oliver, 1925 (Box-folder 9-677)
    - O'Shaughnessy, 1925 (Box-folder 9-678)
    - J.R. Parrott, 1925 (Box-folder 9-679)
    - E.R. Price, 1925 (Box-folder 9-680)
    - H.R. Price, 1925 (Box-folder 9-681)
    - S.R. Pritchard, 1925 (Box-folder 9-682)
    - W.R. Rasche, 1925 (Box-folder 9-683)
    - Ellen A. Reynolds, 1925 (Box-folder 9-684)
    - F.L. Robeson, 1925 (Box-folder 9-685)
    - R.A. Runnells, 1925 (Box-folder 9-686)
    - H.W. Sanders, 1925 (Box-folder 9-687)
    - W.D. Saunders, 1925 (Box-folder 9-688)
    - W.J. Schoene, 1925 (Box-folder 9-689)
    - C.E. Seitz, 1925 (Box-folder 9-690)
      - Blueprint for Proposed Ag. Eng. Group
    - A.G. Smith, 1925 (Box-folder 9-691)
    - E.A. Smyth, 1925 (Box-folder 9-692)
    - H.S. Stahl, 1925 (Box-folder 9-693)
    - J. Hop Taft, 1925 (Box-folder 9-694)
    - C.C. Taylor, 1925 (Box-folder 9-695)
    - B.H. Van Oot, 1925 (Box-folder 9-696)
    - Maggie M. Wade, 1925 (Box-folder 9-697)
    - Roy D. Walston, 1925 (Box-folder 9-698)
    - J.W. Watson, 1925 (Box-folder 9-699)
    - J.E. Williams, 1925 (Box-folder 9-700)
    - I.D. Wilson, 1925 (Box-folder 9-701)
    - T.K. Wolfe, 1925 (Box-folder 9-702)
    - Helen M. Woodruff, 1925 (Box-folder 9-703)
  - Subseries 9: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1925
    - Miscellaneous A, 1925 (Box-folder 9-704)
    - Mrs. Ora Hart Avery - Home Economics, 1925 (Box-folder 9-705)
    - Miscellaneous B, 1925 (Box-folder 9-706)
    - J.H. Bradford, Director of the Budget, 1925 (Box-folder 9-707)
    - Miscellaneous C, 1925 (Box-folder 9-708)
    - Miscellaneous D, 1925 (Box-folder 9-709)
    - F. W. Eheart, 1925 (Box-folder 9-710)
    - Miscellaneous F, 1925 (Box-folder 9-711)
    - Miscellaneous G, 1925 (Box-folder 9-712)
    - Miscellaneous H, 1925 (Box-folder 9-713)
    - Miscellaneous J, 1925 (Box-folder 9-714)
    - D. K. Kellogg, 1925 (Box-folder 9-715)
    - Miscellaneous L, 1925 (Box-folder 9-716)
    - Miscellaneous M, 1925 (Box-folder 9-717)
    - Warren H. Manning, 1925 (Box-folder 9-718)
    - J. L. Newcom, 1925 (Box-folder 9-719)
    - R. L. Olinger, 1925 (Box-folder 9-720)
    - Lawrence Priddy Chairman Building Comm./World War Memorial Hall, 1925 (Box-folder 9-721)
    - G. S. Ralston, 1925 (Box-folder 9-722)
    - Slusser Brothers Land & Coal Option - mineral rights, 1925 (Box-folder 9-723)
    - W.W. Sale Adjutant General, 1925 (Box-folder 9-724)
    - W. P. Tamg, 1925 (Box-folder 9-725)
    - E. Lee Trinkle, 1925 (Box-folder 9-726)
    - Veterans Bureau, 1925 (Box-folder 9-727)
    - War Department, 1925 (Box-folder 9-728)
      - letter from Gen. D. MacArthur to VPI
  - Subseries 10: Faculty Correspondence, 1926
    - G.T. Baird, 1926 (Box-folder 9-729)
    - W.M. Brodie, 1926 (Box-folder 9-730)
    - W.A. Brumfield, 1926 (Box-folder 9-731)
    - R.M. Brown, 1926 (Box-folder 9-732)
    - C.T. Cornman, 1926 (Box-folder 9-733)
    - Dance Matters, 1926 (Box-folder 9-734)
    - Martha D. Dinwiddie, 1926 (Box-folder 9-735)
      - Women Students
    - A.W. Drinkard, 1926 (Box-folder 9-736)
    - M.H. Eoff, 1929 (Box-folder 9-737)
    - W.T. Ellis, 1926 (Box-folder 9-738)
    - Faculty Blanket Letters, 1926 (Box-folder 9-739)
    - F.H. Fish, 1926 (Box-folder 9-740)
    - J.B. Fogleman, 1926 (Box-folder 9-741)
    - W.E. Garnett, 1926 (Box-folder 9-742)
    - James Gadkin, 1926 (Box-folder 9-743)
    - H. Gudheim, 1926 (Box-folder 9-744)
    - C.W. Holdaway, 1926 (Box-folder 9-745)
    - R.J. Holden, 1926 (Box-folder 9-746)
    - Anna G. Hannas, 1926 (Box-folder 9-747)
    - M.C. Harrison, 1926 (Box-folder 9-748)
    - H.H. Hill, 1926 (Box-folder 9-749)
    - J.R. Hutcheson 1/1/26 - 6/30/26 (Box-folder 9-750)
    - J.R. Hutcheson 7/1/26 - 12/31/26 (Box-folder 9-751)
    - T.B. Hutcheson, 1926 (Box-folder 9-752)
    - J.S.A. Johnson, 1926 (Box-folder 9-753)
    - T.W. Knote, 1926 (Box-folder 9-754)
    - A.R. MacMillan, 1926 (Box-folder 9-755)
    - Mrs. J.B. McBryde (Box-folder 9-756)
    - M.B. McGowan, 1926 (Box-folder 9-757)
    - E.C. Magill, 1926 (Box-folder 9-758)
    - E. C. Miller, 1926 (Box-folder 9-759 and 9-759A)
    - C.P. Miles, 1926 (Box-folder 9-760)
    - F.A. Motz, 1926 (Box-folder 9-761)
    - C.M. Newman, Chairman Committee on Social Act., 1926 (Box-folder 9-762)
    - W.R. Nichols, 1926 (Box-folder 9-763)
    - Vernon O'Johns, 1926 (Box-folder 9-764)
    - E.R. Price, 1926 (Box-folder 9-765)
    - H.L. Price, 1926 (Box-folder 9-766)
    - S.R. Pritchard, 1926 (Box-folder 9-767)
    - W.H. Rasche, 1926 (Box-folder 9-768)
    - H.B. Redd, 1926 (Box-folder 10-769)
    - W.J. Schoene, 1926 (Box-folder 10-770)
    - C.E. Seitz (Box-folder 10-771)
    - J.F.D. Smith, 1926 (Box-folder 10-772)
    - J.W. Watson, 1926 (Box-folder 10-773)
    - J.E. Williams, 1926 (Box-folder 10-774)
  - Subseries 11: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1926
    - Miscellaneous A, 1926 (Box-folder 10-775)
    - Miscellaneous B, 1926 (Box-folder 10-776)
    - Harry Flood Byrd, Governor of Virginia, 1926 (Box-folder 10-777)
    - J.H. Bradford, Director of the Budget, 1926 (Box-folder 10-778)
    - Miscellaneous C, 1926 (Box-folder 10-779)
    - Miscellaneous D, 1926 (Box-folder 10-780)
    - Miscellaneous E, 1926 (Box-folder 10-781)
    - Miscellaneous F, 1926 (Box-folder 10-782)
    - Miscellaneous G, 1926 (Box-folder 10-783)
    - Miscellaneous H, 1926 (Box-folder 10-784)
    - Miscellaneous J, 1926 (Box-folder 10-785)
    - Hugh Kerr, 1926 (Box-folder 10-786)
    - Geo. W. Koiner, Commissioner of Agriculture, 1926 (Box-folder 10-787)
    - Miscellaneous L, 1926 (Box-folder 10-788)
    - Miscellaneous M, 1926 (Box-folder 10-789)
    - Warren H. Manning, 1926 (Box-folder 10-790)
    - Miscellaneous N, 1926 (Box-folder 10-791)
    - R.F. Nelson, 1926 (Box-folder 10-792)
    - Chas. A. Osborne, State Purchasing Agent, 1926 (Box-folder 10-793)
    - Miscellaneous P, 1926 (Box-folder 10-794)
    - Lawrence Priddy 1/1/26 - 6/30/26 (Box-folder 10-795)
    - Lawrence Priddy 7/1/26 - 12/31/26 (Box-folder 10-796)
    - Miscellaneous R, 1926 (Box-folder 10-797)
    - Miscellaneous S, 1926 (Box-folder 10-798)
      - Latin American students
      - Women students
    - I. L. Spear, 1926 (Box-folder 10-799)
    - Miscellaneous T, 1926 (Box-folder 10-800)
    - B.H. Van Oot, 1926 (Box-folder 10-801)
    - Miscellaneous W, 1926 (Box-folder 10-802)
      - Water systems and septic tanks
      - Typhoid Fever
      - Aerial League of America - letters re: Byrd and Bennett, First to fly to North Pole
  - Subseries 12: Correspondence, 1927
    - Kent Apperson, 1927 (Box-folder 10-803)
    - Ilena M. Bailey, 1927 (Box-folder 10-804)
    - G.T. Baird, 1927 (Box-folder 10-805)
    - W.E. Barlow, 1927 (Box-folder 10-806)
    - R.B.H. Begg, 1927 (Box-folder 10-807)
    - R.M. Brown, 1927 (Box-folder 10-808)
    - W.A. Brumfield, 1927 (Box-folder 10-809)
    - F.A. Buchanan, 1927 (Box-folder 10-810)
    - O.C. Burkhart, 1927 (Box-folder 10-811)
    - W.H. Byrne, 1927 (Box-folder 10-812)
    - T.P. Campbell, 1927 (Box-folder 10-813)
    - W.M. Chapin, 1927 (Box-folder 10-814)
    - The Chaplains, 1927 (Box-folder 10-815)
    - Melria Chapman, 1927 (Box-folder 10-816)
    - W.B. Coggin, 1927 (Box-folder 10-817)
    - W.G. Conner, 1927 (Box-folder 10-818)
    - A.L. Dean, 1927 (Box-folder 10-819)
    - H.P. Detwiler, 1927 (Box-folder 10-820)
    - Martha D. Dinwiddie, 1927 (Box-folder 10-821)
    - A.W. Drinkard, 1927 (Box-folder 10-822)
    - Agriculture and Crops (Box-folder 10-822A)